Guide to the Toba Pato Tucker Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Project Files, circa 1950-2005; Series II; (41 boxes)
  - Heber Springs Portraits
    - Products
      - Heber Springs Portraits: Continuity and Change in the World Disfarmer Photographed (1996)
        Materials compiled by Tucker for the book. It includes photocopies of images created by Mike Disfarmer and a list of the images created by Tucker and used in the book. It also includes draft essays by her and Alan Trachtenberg for the work, the preface by Helen A. Harrison, and an unpublished essay by Gene Thornton, and galley proofs of the book, as well as a copy of the book signed by many of the portrait subjects
        - Images by Mike Disfarmer, circa 1994 (Box 217, Folder 2963)
        - Portrait subjects, circa 1994 (Box 217, Folder 2964)
        - Essays
          - Helen A. Harrison, 1986, circa 1994 (Box 217, Folder 2965)
          - Gene Thornton, circa 1994 (Box 217, Folder 2966)
          - Alan Trachtenberg, 1994 June (Box 217, Folder 2967-2968)
          - Toba Tucker, circa 1994 (Box 217, Folder 2969)
        - Dummy, circa 1995 (Box 217, Folder 2970-2972)
        - Galley, 1996 July 3 (Box 217, Folder 2973)
        - Book, 1996 (Box 217, Folder 2974-2975)
          Includes a clothbound volume inscribed by Tucker and several portrait subjects, and a disbound paperback volume used by Tucker to digitize the images and create a website
        - Publicity, 1996 (Box 217, Folder 2976)
          Includes informal portraits of Tucker and Dana Asbury, an editor at University of New Mexico Press
        - Sale orders, 1996 September-2002 September (Box 217, Folder 2977)
  - Onondaga Nation Portraits
    - Background research, 1987-1991 (Box 218, Folder 2978)
      - The Faithkeeper, Oren Lyons with Bill Moyers (videocassette), 1991 July 3; WAMSSS2604_0001; 1; 00:57:27 (Box 218, Item barcode 39002093672633)
        Interview of Oren Lyons by Bill Moyers for Public Affairs Television, Inc.
        Accompanied by a transcript of the interview.
        Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult access services for further information.
    - Correspondence, 1991 August-2006 April (Box 218, Folder 2980)
    - Portrait subjects
      - Releases, 1991 June-1992 June (Box 218, Folder 2981)
      - Interviews [audiotape recordings]
        - Audrey Shenandoah, 1991 November; 1; 00:38:46; The program ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard. (Box 218, Item barcode 39002091249699)
          Onondaga elder and Deer Clan mother
          Running time Side A (only): 39 minutes
        - Jessica Jeanne "Jeannie" Shenandoah, 1991 November; 1; 00:17:51; The program begins and ends abruptly. (Box 218, Item barcode 39002091249707)
          Daughter of Audrey Shenandoah and a midwife, herbalist and teacher
    - Products
      - Exhibitions and lectures
        - Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, New York, 1994 May 20- August 28 (Box 218, Folder 2984)
        - New York Historical Association, Cooperstown, New York, 1999 October 28 (Box 218, Folder 2985)
      - Serial publications
        - Contact Sheet, No. 72, 1991 (Box 218, Folder 2986)
        - Life, 1994 August (Box 218, Folder 2987)
        - Native Peoples, 1994 Fall (Box 218, Folder 2988)
      - Haudenosaunee: Portraits of the Firekeepers, the Onondaga Nation (1996)
        Materials compiled by Tucker for the book. It includes a list of the images created by Tucker and used in the book. It also includes a draft essays by Irving Powless, book dummies, and galley proofs of the book, and a copy of the book signed by some of the portrait subjects
        - Portrait subjects, circa 1998 (Box 219, Folder 2989)
        - Book illustrations, circa 1998 (Box 219, Folder 2990)
        - Essay by Irving Powless, Jr., circa 1998 (Box 219, Folder 2991)
          Powless is a leader of the Beaver Clan of the Onondaga
        - Dummies, circa 1998 (Box 219, Folder 2992-2993)
        - Galley and figure proofs, 1999 (Box 219, Folder 2994-2996)
        - Book, 1999 (Box 219, Folder 2997)
        - Publicity, 1999-2001 (Box 219, Folder 2998)
          - Hodinonshonni: The Onondaga Nation- Portraits of the Firekeepers by Toba Pato Tucker, video news release and :30 PSA, circa 1999; WAMSSS2604_0002; 1; 00:25:36 (Box 219, Item barcode 39002093672641)
            The video includes eight soundbites (interviews with the artist) and video of the exhibit and other related material. A 30-second PSA can be found beginning at 00:24:12.
        - Book orders, 2001-2006 (Box 219, Folder 3000)
  - Pueblo Artists, Portraits
    - Background
      - Project proposal with Bruce David Bernstein, circa 1995 (Box 220, Folder 3001)
        Bernstein was director and chief curator at the Museum of New Mexico in Santa Fe
      - Overview of collected material, circa 1996 (Box 220, Folder 3002)
      - Pueblos, 1996-1997 (Box 220, Folder 3003)
      - Notebook, 1996 (Box 220, Folder 3004)
      - Southwestern Association for Indian Artists, circa 1995 (Box 220, Folder 3005)
      - Contacts, 1995-1996 (Box 220, Folder 3006-3010)
      - Publications, 1991-1997 (Box 221, Folder 3011)
    - Correspondence
      - Sample letters, 1995 (Box 221, Folder 3012)
      - General, 1995-2003, undated (Box 221, Folder 3013-3016)
      - Portrait subjects, 1995-1999 (Box 221, Folder 3017)
    - Releases, 1995 May-1997 June (Box 221, Folder 3018-3019)
    - Products
      - Exhibitions
        - Governor's Gallery, New Mexico Museum of Art, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1997 July 11- August 22 (Box 222, Folder 3020)
        - New York State Historical Association, Cooperstown, New York, 1998 April 1-1999 January (Box 222, Folder 3021)
        - Wheelwright Museum of The American Indian, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1998 August 18- September 28 (Box 222, Folder 3022)
        - Southwest Museum for Native American Art, Los Angeles, California, 1998 September 26-1999 January (Box 222, Folder 3023)
        - Exhibit labels, 1997-1998 (Box 222, Folder 3024-3025)
      - Pueblo Artists: Portraits (1998)
        Materials compiled by Tucker for the book.
        - Book proposal dummy, 1996 (Box 223, Folder 3026)
        - Portrait lists, 1997 (Box 223, Folder 3027-3028)
        - Essay drafts, 1997 (Box 223, Folder 3029)
        - Image captions, 1997 (Box 223, Folder 3030)
        - Image galleys, 1998 (Box 223, Folder 3031-3032)
        - Book sample to publisher, 1998 (Box 223, Folder 3033-3034)
        - Book dummy, 1998 (Box 223-224, Folder 3035-3037)
        - Final book text, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 3038)
        - Publisher's book dummy, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 3039)
        - Book, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 3040)
          Includes a clothbound volume inscribed by Tucker and several portrait subjects
        - Public relations, 1998-2002 (Box 224, Folder 3041-3043)
        - Book reviews, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 3044)
        - Personal book orders, 1999-2002 (Box 224, Folder 3045)
        - Royalty statements, 1999-2005 (Box 224, Folder 3046)
  - Native American Relocation Project, 1999 August- September
    - Background and correspondence, 1999 -2001 (Box 225, Folder 3047)
    - Releases, 2001 February 3 (Box 225, Folder 3048)
    - Portrait lists, 2001 (Box 225, Folder 3049)
  - Commissioned Portraits
    - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 226, Folder 3050)
    - Releases, 1983 (Box 226, Folder 3051)
    - Negative list and printing information, 1982 August1987 August- (Box 226, Folder 3052)
    - Pollock-Krasner House and Studio, East Hampton, New York., 1996 (Box 226, Folder 3053)
    - Advertising, circa 1987-2003 (Box 226, Folder 3054-3055)
      - Prints used for website, circa 2004 (Box 226, Folder 3056)
  - Additional Projects
    - Montaukett Indian Portraits, 1986 December, 1988 Jan-Mar (Box 227, Folder 3057)
    - Australian Aboriginal Art and Artists, 1992 December-1999 July (Box 227, Folder 3058)
    - Mashantucket Pequot Tribe, 1994 November (Box 227, Folder 3059)
    - Jewish Heritage and Diaspora, 1996-1999 (Box 227, Folder 3060)
    - Mohegan Tribe, 1997 December (Box 227, Folder 3061)
    - Native Americans in the Arts, 1997 December-2000 Feb (Box 227, Folder 3062)
    - Native Americans in the Pacific Northwest, 1998-2000 (Box 227, Folder 3063)
    - Alaskan Natives, 2000 April (Box 227, Folder 3064)
    - Mormon Community in New York, New York, 2000 May-November (Box 227, Folder 3065)
    - Pueblo of Pojoaque, 2002 September-November (Box 227, Folder 3066)
    - Pueblo Indian Military Veterans, 2004-2005 (Box 227, Folder 3067)
  - Personal Portraits
    - Portrait releases, 1980 August-1987 April (Box 228, Folder 3068)
    - Printing notes
      - Portraits, 1978 August-1987 April (Box 228, Folder 3069)
      - Seascapes, 1986 August-1986 November (Box 228, Folder 3070)
      - Body builders, 1986 March-1987 March (Box 228, Folder 3071)
    - Exhibitions and lectures
      This subseries includes group exhibitions that Tucker took part in and lectures by her that did not focus on a particular project. Lectures have a date with a single day
      - Soho Photo Foundation, New York, New York, 1975 May 4-June 1, 1977 September 6-27 (Box 228, Folder 3072-3073)
      - Philadelphia Art Alliance, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1978 February 20-Mar 26 (Box 228, Folder 3074)
      - Musée Français de la Photographic, Bièvres, France, 1978 May-June (Box 228, Folder 3075)
      - Woodman Gallery, Morristown, New Jersey, 1979 October 23-November 30 (Box 228, Folder 3076)
      - East Galleries, New York University, New York, New York, 1979 October 9-November 2 (Box 228, Folder 3077)
      - Light Gallery, New York, New York, 1981 July 9- August 28 (Box 228, Folder 3078)
      - Omnihealth and Racquet Club, Southampton, New York, 1987 May 2- September 7 (Box 228, Folder 3079)
      - Marine Museum, Amagansett, New York, 1987 July 19- September 7 (Box 228, Folder 3080)
      - New York Public Library, New York, New York, 1992 October -1993 January 30 (Box 228, Folder 3081)
      - Richmond Art Center Gallery, Loomis Chafee School, Windsor, Connecticut, 1994 November 14- December 17 (Box 228, Folder 3082)
      - Sweeney Convention Center, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1996 July 11-14 (Box 228, Folder 3083)
      - Springs School and Pierson High School, East Hampton, New York, 1998 February 24 (Box 228, Folder 3084)
      - Islip Art Museum, East Islip, New York, 1998 June 27- September (Box 228, Folder 3085)
      - Art Fair in Los Angeles, California, 2002 Feb (Box 228, Folder 3086)
      - Center for Contemporary Arts, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2003 July 8 (Box 228, Folder 3087)
      - New Mexico State Capitol, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2003 July 11- September 20 (Box 228, Folder 3088)
      - Gerald Peters Gallery, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2004 May 14-22 (Box 228, Folder 3089)
        Exhibition for the Heart Gallery, portraits of children awaiting adoption in New Mexico
      - St. John's College Art Gallery, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2004 August 13- September 13 (Box 228, Folder 3090)
      - Absolute Americana Art Gallery, St. Augustine, Florida, 2005 August 20-October31 (Box 228, Folder 3091)
    - Permanent Collections, 1971-1999 (Box 228, Folder 3092)
    - Publication: "The Question of Beauty," Ms.(magazine), 1983 May (Box 228, Folder 3093)
    - Public relations: Presentation of all projects, circa 2003 (Box 228, Folder 3094)
  - Oversize
    - Navajo Portraits
      - Certificate for Arts Directors Club Merit Award for a publication in Popular Photography, 1983 (Box 229, Folder 3095)
    - Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits
      - Publicity, 1987 August-1993 August (Box 229, Folder 3096)
    - Black History & Folklife Project, Riverhead, New York
      - Publicity, 1986 December-1987 January (Box 229, Folder 3097)
    - Heber Springs Portraits
      - Book jacket galley, 1996 July (Box 229, Folder 3098)
      - Publicity, 1996 November (Box 229, Folder 3099)
    - Onondaga Nation Portraits
      - Printing templates, circa 1994 (Box 229, Folder 3100)
      - Exhibition. Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, New York, 1994 May 20- August 28 (Box 229, Folder 3101)
      - Illustrations for book, circa 1976-circa 1998 (Box 229, Folder 3102)
      - Book jacket galley, circa 1998 (Box 229, Folder 3103)
      - Book orders and royalties, 1998 June-2000 December (Box 229, Folder 3104)
      - Publication. 1998 Peace Calendar, Syracuse Cultural Workers (Box 229, Folder 3105)
    - Pueblo Artists, Portraits
      - Background, 1995-1997 (Box 230, Folder 3106)
      - Book jacket galley, 1998 (Box 230, Folder 3107)
      - Publisher proofs, 1998 (Box 230, Folder 3108)
      - Ink jet prints made at Santa Fe Photographic Workshops, 1996 June 15 (Box 230, Folder 3109)
        Also includes some family photographs and Navajo Portraits
      - Publicity, 1996 August-November (Box 230, Folder 3110)
    - Personal
      - Musée Français de la Photographic, Bièvres, France, 1978 May-June (Box 230, Folder 3111)
    - Maps, circa 1980-1990 (Box 253 (Broadside), Folder 3112)
      Chiefly interstate highway maps and municipal maps used by Tucker in the course of her projects, as well as maps published by National Geographic Magazine
- Personal and Professional Papers, circa 1965-2006; Series III; (7 boxes)
  Series III is organized into eleven subseries: Correspondence, Calendars, General Papers, Employment, Grant and Institutional Funding, Publications About Tucker, Video Recordings About Tucker, Financial Records, Photography Equipment, Biographical Files About Other Artists, and Publications that Include Images by Tucker.
  Series III includes papers not directly connected with a single photographic project and generally document her career as a professional photographer.
  Box 216 contains audiovisual material. Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence, 1973 September-2006 April 18 (Box 231, Folder 3113-3116)
    The correspondence consists primarily of professional correspondence realted to her photography.
  - Calendars, 1977-2004 (Box 232-233, Folder 3117-3132)
    Daily calendars documenting photography projects, exhibitions, and personal appointments.
    Lacks calendars for 1980 to 1982, 1988, and 1992
  - General Papers
    - Family, circa 1965-circa 2006 (Box 234, Folder 3133)
    - Copy ink jet prints of family photographs, 1953-2005, circa 2006 (Box 234, Folder 3134)
    - Friends, 2006 May 30 (Box 234, Folder 3135)
      - Audiotape conversation between Tucker and Toby Olds, 1978 November 8; 1; 00:31:47; The program ends abruptly. Static can be heard on the tape. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 234, Item barcode 39002091249715)
      - Audiotape conversation between Tucker and Joel Sternfield, 1980 April 19; 1; 01:10:51; The program begins abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 234, Item barcode 39002091249723)
        Running time Side B: 24 minutes
    - Astrological charts, 1985 March (Box 234, Folder 3138)
    - Certificates, 1972-2004 (Box 234, Folder 3139)
    - Business cards, circa 1977-circa 2006 (Box 234, Folder 3140)
    - Health effects of photography, 1996 October (Box 234, Folder 3141)
  - Employment
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, New York, New York, 1971-1974 (Box 234, Folder 3142)
    - Resumes and biographical information, circa 2004 (Box 234, Folder 3143)
  - Grant and Institutional Funding
    - American Museum of Natural History, New York, New York, 1997 December-1998 October (Box 234, Folder 3144)
    - California Community Foundation, 2001 (Box 234, Folder 3145)
    - Erna and Victor Hasselblad Foundation, 2002 (Box 234, Folder 3146)
    - Eugene V. and Clare E. Thaw Charitable Trust, 1995 October (Box 234, Folder 3147)
    - Dorothea Lange - Paul Taylor Prize, Center for Documentary Studies, Duke University, 1996 Jan- April (Box 234, Folder 3148)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, circa 1992 (Box 234, Folder 3149)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1981-1996 (Box 234, Folder 3150)
    - Los Angeles, California, and Arizona, area museums, universities, and art galleries, 2000 April-October (Box 234, Folder 3151)
    - MacDowell Colony, Peterborough, New Hampshire, 1997 April (Box 234, Folder 3152)
    - McCune Foundation, 1995 December-1996 March (Box 234, Folder 3153)
    - Museum of New Mexico Foundation, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 234, Folder 3154)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1996 October-1997 March (Box 234, Folder 3155)
    - New Mexico Council on Photography, 1996 (Box 234, Folder 3156)
    - New Mexico Endowment for the Humanities, 1996 May (Box 234, Folder 3157)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1979-1990 (Box 234, Folder 3158)
    - New York Historical Association, 1997 December-1999 January (Box 234, Folder 3159)
    - Polo Ralph Lauren Foundation, 1997 May (Box 234, Folder 3160)
    - Richard Florsheim Art Fund, 1995 September-1996 April (Box 234, Folder 3161)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation Bellagio Center, 1996 August-1997 January (Box 234, Folder 3162)
    - Thanks be to Grandmother Winifred Foundation, 1995 May-1997 August (Box 234, Folder 3163)
    - Washington, District of Columbia, area museums, universities, and art galleries, 1991 April, circa 1998 (Box 234, Folder 3164)
  - Publications About Tucker
    - "Toba Tucker: Photographs," X: International Review of Arts and Culture, 1994 Winter (Box 235, Folder 3165)
    - Jay Jorgensen, "Toba Tucker: Portrait of the Photographer," Petersen's Photographic, 2001 April (Box 235, Folder 3166)
    - "The Art and Craft of Black and White Photography: A Roundtable Discussion with Audrey Hall, Rick Murai, and Toba Tucker," Camera Arts, 2003 April-May (Box 235, Folder 3167)
  - Video Recordings About Tucker
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Meet You Neighbor, Neighbor. Toba Tucker and Jeff Potter, 1987 June 29; WAMSSS2604_0007; 1; 00:30:37 (Box 216, Item barcode 39002093672690)
      A note included with the tape reads: Jeff Potter is an editor of the Shelburne Falls Independent newspaper.
    - Toba Tucker photo presentation, undated; WAMSSS2604_0008; 1; 00:51:22 (Box 216, Item barcode 39002093672708)
  - Financial Records
    Restricted material. May not be seen without the permission of the appropriate curator.
    - Copyright registrations, 1979 December-1997 February (Box 236, Folder 3170)
    - Tax forms, 1994-1997 (Box 236, Folder 3171)
      This folder contains papers restricted until after the death of Toba Pato Tucker. For further information consult the Curator of the Yale Collection of Western Americana.
    - Social Security earnings and benefits, 1995 June-1997 February (Box 236, Folder 3172)
    - Retail and information Internet websites about her books, 2004 March-2005 November (Box 236, Folder 3173)
  - Photography Equipment (Box 236, Folder 3174-3175)
    Documents related to photographic equipment used by Tucker
  - Biographical Files About Other Artists
    - Antonio Alamilla Carmona, circa 1980 (Box 236, Folder 3176)
      Carmona was married to Tucker's sister, Barbara Pato
    - Harold Feinstein, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 3177)
    - George Gabin, 1963 September-1967 May (Box 236, Folder 3178)
    - Peter Matthiessen, circa 1991 (Box 236, Folder 3179)
  - Publications that Include Images by Tucker, 10 volumes (Box 237)
    Examples of publications that reproduced photographs by Tucker. The entries include the page numbers for her imagery.
    - Barr, Tom, and Marsha Bol. North, South, East, West: American Indians and the Natural World. Boulder: Roberts Rinehart Publishers, 1998. Page xiii. (Box 237)
    - Bramly, Serge. Indianer Nordamerikas: Photographien und kolorierte Stiche von Edward S. Curtis, Karl Bodmer, Frank A. Rinehart und zeitgenössischen Photographien. Baden: L. Müller, 1993. Pages 76-77. (Box 237)
    - Giard, Robert. The Grandmother Winifred Journals: 1996-2002. Sag Harbor, N.Y.: Crones' Cradle Conserve Press, 2005. Page 193. (Box 237)
      This image is a porrait by Robert Giard of Tucker posed with several exhibitition prints from the Pueblo Artists, Portraits, series.
    - Gore, Albert, and Tipper Gore. The Spirit of Family. New York: H. Holt, 2002. Page 8. (Box 237)
    - Harlow, Francis H., and Dwight P. Lanmon. The Pottery of Zia Pueblo. Santa Fe, N.M.: School of American Research Press, 2003. Page 279. (Box 237)
    - Johnson, Tim. Spirit Capture: Photographs from the National Museum of the American Indian. Washington: Smithsonian Institution Press in association with the National Museum of the American Indian, Smithsonian Institution, 1998. Page 57 and back of dustjacket. (Box 237)
    - Light Work. Contact Sheet 97: 25th Anniversary Edition. Syracuse, N.Y.: Light Work, 1998. Page 74 (Box 237)
    - London, Barbara, and John Upton. Photography. New York: Longman, 1998. Page 319 (Box 237)
    - Schlissel, Lillian, and Catherine Jane Lavender. The Western Women's Reader. New York: HarperPerennial, 2000. Page 547. (Box 237)
    - Strong, John A. "We Are Still Here!": The Algonquian Peoples of Long Island Today. Interlaken, N.Y.: Empire State Books, 1996. Pages 66-67. (Box 237)
- Additions, 2008-2011, 1995-2011; Series IV; (14 boxes)
  This Series IV is organized into three subseries: Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits, Landscapes of the American West, and Photographs of Africa.
  This series consists of photographic materials created by Tucker since the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library acquired the bulk of her collection in 2007-2008. It includes exhibition and work prints of Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits, as well as exhibition prints of Landscapes of the American West and Photographs of Africa.
  - Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits, 4 boxes
    Arranged in the order established by the photographer, which loosely follows the order in which she photographed the sitters, except for a portrait of Sierra Sky Gumbs.
    Purchased from Toba Pato Tucker on the Walter McClintock Memorial Fund, 2010.
    Portraits of Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island created by Tucker June 22-24, 1995, printed by Alissa Marquis of Santa Fe, New Mexico, in 2010.
    Manuscript titles and signatures on rectos of the prints.
    Related Archival Materials note
    Associated Materials: Negatives for these photographs are in Series I. Photographs, Negatives and Contact Sheets, Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits
    - Exhibition Prints, 16 inches by 20 inches
      - Starleaf Anita Gumbs, Sunshine Kim Gumbs, and Sierra Sky Gumbs, 1995 June 22 (Box 238, Folder 3180)
      - Starleaf Anita Gumbs, 1995 June 22 (Box 238, Folder 3181)
      - Starleaf Anita Gumbs and Sunshine Kim Gumbs, 1995 June 22 (Box 238, Folder 3182)
      - Gregory Marshall, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3183)
      - Robert Eleazer and Yatch Bess Eleazer, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3184)
      - Robert Eleazer, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3185)
      - James W. Eleazer, III, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3186)
      - Frederick "Red" Lincoln, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3187)
      - Ginew Benton-Smith and Mataugus Tarrant, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3188)
      - Ahneah Hill, Rainbow Hill, Rebecca Hill, and Yatch Bess Eleazer, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3189)
      - Ahneah Hill, Rainbow Hill, and Rebecca Hill, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3190)
      - Kia Loni Gordon, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3191-3192)
      - Lubin Hunter, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3193)
      - Kia Loni Gordon, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3194)
      - Meesha Johnson, 1995 June 23 (Box 238, Folder 3195)
      - Adam Phillips, 1995 June 23 (Box 239, Folder 3196)